

Eindhoven, the Netherlands

🛘 (+31) 6 4820 9406 | 🗷 cas@eliens.co | 🏕 cas.eliens.co | 🖸 cascer1 | 🖹 cas-eliëns | 🛅 caseliens

"Truth can only be found in one place: the code."

Summary _

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history in backend development.

Skilled in Java, PHP, Deployment, and Customer Service. Strong software professional with a Bachelor of Information & Communication Technology focused in Computer Software Engineering and Cyber Security from Fontys Hogescholen.

Experience _____

ISAAC Eindhoven, NL

DEVELOPER

Sep 2018 - Current · Develop Java API back-end for financial applications

Sharegroup B.V. NL

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT & LEAD BACK-END DEVELOPER

• Develop API back-end for Soundshare platform

Duco Hosting Eindhoven, NL OWNER Apr 2013 - Dec 2020

· Managed hosting infrastructure and servers

- Linux server security and configuration
- Managed DNS and other domain configurations

ISAAC Eindhoven, NL

INTERN JAVA DEVELOPMENT

Aug 2016 - Jan 2017

 Developed automated API documentation tooling for RAML and Swagger • Researched iDin authentication for secure financial logins

HEMA Eindhoven, NL

Nov 2010 - Aug 2018 SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Maintain proper stocking levels for internal consumables like receipt paper and office supplies
- · Applied and maintained in-store promotional material

Education

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Fontys Hogeschool ICT Eindhoven, NL

· Completed courses toward a bachelor in Software Engineering

• Participated in the Fontys ICT Delta excellence program

Certifications

Microsoft Online

MICROSOFT AZURE DEVELOPER ASSOCIATE Dec 2020 - Dec 2022

- View Certification
- Credential ID H617-9431

Amazon Web Services (AWS) AWS CERTIFIED DEVELOPER ASSOCIATE

Online

2014 - 2018

Sep 2020 - Sep 2023

Dec 2017 - Current

· View Certification

CAS ELIËNS · RÉSUMÉ

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Online

AWS CLOUD PRACTITIONER ESSENTIALS (SECOND EDITION) May 2020

Oracle Online

ORACLE CERTIFIED PROFESSIONAL, JAVA SE 8 PROGRAMMER Dec 2019

· View Certification

Oracle Online

ORACLE CERTIFIED ASSOCIATE, JAVA SE 8 PROGRAMMER Feb 2019

· View Certification

University of Cambridge Eindhoven, NL

CEFR ENGLISH - LEVEL C2

Jan 2014 • Credential ID ZEF281600

Extracurricular Activity

reddit.com/r/diabetes online

COMMUNITY MODERATOR May 2017 - current

- Moderate popular chat platform for a diabetes support group.
- Provide helpful insights and support in diabetes care.
- Moderate the r/diabetes community on Reddit.
- Help protect the community from unwelcome content.

Writing.

WRITER

Why every diabetic should switch to a closed-loop system

medium.com/@cas.eliens/bd520c732dc1

Apr 2018

- Describe advantages of automation in diabetes management
- Give real-life examples of automation results in diabetes management